(Leonard:)...on Billy the Kid's cowboy hat?
(Howard:)What? Please.
This is Billy the Kid we're talking about.
(Howard:)The wizard would get shot
before he could get out the words:
"What the hell is Billy the Kid doing
in the mystic realm of Ka'a?"
Leonard, ahem...
(Stuart:)...what's the deal
with Sheldon's friend Amy?
(Stuart:)- Are they a couple?
- A couple of weirdos. Why?
Are you interested in Amy?
(Stuart:)Well, I mean,
she didn't look through me...
(Stuart:)...with soul-sucking, ball-shriveling
hatred and contempt.
(Stuart:)I like that in a woman.
(Stuart:)Could you run it by Sheldon
if I could ask her out?
(Leonard:)Sure, I guess.
(Raj:)Stuart, settle an argument for us.
(Raj:)Who would win,
Billy the Kid or the white Wizard?
(Stuart:)If I tell you that, I'm robbing you
of the hours of fun you could have...
(Stuart:)...for the magical, rootin'- tootin
Iow price of 24.95.
- I'll take one.
- Mm. Make it two.
I hate all of you and myseIf. Three.
(Stuart:)I'll ring it up.
(Stuart:)Like shooting nerds in a barrel.